{
    "id": "db1c81d62e8e460ab308ddb06ce6ff1b",
    "title": "In Case And In Case Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have bought some eggs .................................... the guests stay to lunch.",
            "description": "In case is mainly used to talk about precautions.",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We will buy a chicken ........................................ the guests stay to lunch.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition - something which must happen first so that something else can happen. In case is mainly used to talk about precautions. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "in case",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me a call ...................................... you have doubts.",
            "description": "In case is a conjunction. It is followed by a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The fire alarm will ring ..................................... fire erupts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Call me .................................... there is a problem.",
            "description": "We use in case before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam will be postponed ......................................... there is a bus strike tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The possession will be stopped ....................................... trouble.",
            "description": "Use in case of before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Break glass ......................................  fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Show this to her ...................................... she asks for proof.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Call the fire brigade ........................................ a fire outbreak.",
            "description": "We use in case of before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Take the coat ................................. it rains.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}